[{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980261443,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":15400,"timeElapsed":45610},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980269783,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":8339,"timeElapsed":53950},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980279773,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":9989,"timeElapsed":63940},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980283823,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4049,"timeElapsed":67990},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980291564,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":7740,"timeElapsed":75731},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980295614,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":4048,"timeElapsed":79781},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980299087,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":3472,"timeElapsed":83254},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980301067,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":1979,"timeElapsed":85234},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980303976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":2908,"timeElapsed":88143},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980320327,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":15479,"timeElapsed":104494},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980323402,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":3074,"timeElapsed":107569},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980328090,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":4687,"timeElapsed":112257},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980329965,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":1874,"timeElapsed":114132},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980333370,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":3404,"timeElapsed":117537},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980335853,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2482,"timeElapsed":120020},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980338763,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":2909,"timeElapsed":122930},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980340631,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":1867,"timeElapsed":124798},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980343211,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2579,"timeElapsed":127378},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980356096,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":11924,"timeElapsed":140263},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980357963,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1866,"timeElapsed":142130},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980362096,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4132,"timeElapsed":146263},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980365464,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3366,"timeElapsed":149631},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980369296,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3831,"timeElapsed":153463},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980370864,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1567,"timeElapsed":155031},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980373316,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2450,"timeElapsed":157483},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980375574,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2257,"timeElapsed":159741},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980377112,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1537,"timeElapsed":161279},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980387005,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":8977,"timeElapsed":171172},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980390124,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":3118,"timeElapsed":174291},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980398226,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":8100,"timeElapsed":182393},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980399928,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":1701,"timeElapsed":184095},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980402163,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":2234,"timeElapsed":186330},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980403603,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":1439,"timeElapsed":187770},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980405883,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":2279,"timeElapsed":190050},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980408125,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":2241,"timeElapsed":192292},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980411418,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":3292,"timeElapsed":195585},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980420096,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":8032,"timeElapsed":204263},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980421814,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":1716,"timeElapsed":205981},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980424394,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2579,"timeElapsed":208561},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980426636,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2241,"timeElapsed":210803},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980432089,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":5452,"timeElapsed":216256},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980434579,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2489,"timeElapsed":218746},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980437219,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":2639,"timeElapsed":221386},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980439815,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2594,"timeElapsed":223982},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980441719,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1904,"timeElapsed":225886},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980448620,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":6022,"timeElapsed":232786},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980451155,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":2534,"timeElapsed":235322},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980457634,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":6479,"timeElapsed":241801},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980459607,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1972,"timeElapsed":243774},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980461715,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2107,"timeElapsed":245882},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980463125,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":1409,"timeElapsed":247292},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980466628,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3502,"timeElapsed":250795},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980469148,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2519,"timeElapsed":253315},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980470917,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1769,"timeElapsed":255084},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981185608,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":713768,"timeElapsed":969775},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981191901,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6292,"timeElapsed":976068},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981196798,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":4896,"timeElapsed":980965},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981202439,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":5640,"timeElapsed":986606},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981204149,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":1709,"timeElapsed":988316},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981208094,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":3944,"timeElapsed":992261},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981210666,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":2571,"timeElapsed":994833},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981212953,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2286,"timeElapsed":997120},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981214964,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2010,"timeElapsed":999131},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981218976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":4011,"timeElapsed":1003143},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981242745,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":22800,"timeElapsed":1026912},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981244747,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":2001,"timeElapsed":1028914},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981247260,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2511,"timeElapsed":1031427},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981249248,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":1987,"timeElapsed":1033415},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981253005,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3756,"timeElapsed":1037172},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981255556,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2549,"timeElapsed":1039722},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981257836,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":2279,"timeElapsed":1042003},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981259861,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":2024,"timeElapsed":1044028},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981261571,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":1709,"timeElapsed":1045738},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981263401,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":1829,"timeElapsed":1047568},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981268501,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":4214,"timeElapsed":1052668},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981270309,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1807,"timeElapsed":1054476},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981272506,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2197,"timeElapsed":1056673},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981274306,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1799,"timeElapsed":1058473},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981276556,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2249,"timeElapsed":1060723},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981278552,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":1994,"timeElapsed":1062719},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981280156,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1603,"timeElapsed":1064323},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981281769,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1611,"timeElapsed":1065936},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981283232,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1462,"timeElapsed":1067399},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981290942,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":7101,"timeElapsed":1075109},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981293417,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":2475,"timeElapsed":1077584},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981295390,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":1971,"timeElapsed":1079557},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981296687,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":1296,"timeElapsed":1080854},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981298022,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":1334,"timeElapsed":1082189},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981299957,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":1934,"timeElapsed":1084124},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981301967,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":2009,"timeElapsed":1086134},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981303520,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":1551,"timeElapsed":1087687},{"subjectID":"5vjhvdcphn","prolificID":"65181c2f753b188afdddd2c4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ebc87683301514f6d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981304929,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":1409,"timeElapsed":1089096}]